Guide to the Brooklyn, N.Y., Department of Law, Corporation Counsel records 2013.015
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 1: Case Files, 1849-1920; 98.0 linear feet; in 199 manuscripts boxes, 4 flat boxes and 1 flat file drawer
  - Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company - New Utrecht bill (5 of 9), 1894-1895 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company - New Utrecht bill (6 of 9), 1894-1895 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company - New Utrecht bill (7 of 9), 1894-1895 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company - New Utrecht bill (8 of 9), 1894-1895 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company - New Utrecht bill (9 of 9), 1894-1895 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Kramat, Edward B. - 3rd Ave. horse death, 1894-1896 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Langan, Edward A. - Electrical mechanic dismissal, 1894-1903 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Latus, Mary T. - 324 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1894-1904 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Leahey, William C. - 111 North 7th St. property damage, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Leaycraft, William H. - Clerk salary, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Leonard, John J. and Daniel S. - Construction contract dispute, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Liefels, John E. and others - Wallabout Market lease disputes, 1894 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Lindon, Grace Adele - Bond St. sidewalk injury, 1894 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (1 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Includes Grace Denio Litchfield, Henry P. Litchfield, and the Brooklyn Improvement Company
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (2 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (3 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (4 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (5 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (6 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (7 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (8 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (9 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (10 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (11 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Litchfield, Edward H. - Assessment disputes (12 of 12), 1894-1897 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Long Island Railroad Company - Car license fees, 1894 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Long Island Railroad Company - Ocean Parkway tunnel, 1894 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Lynch, Peter C. - Inspector of streets salary (1 of 2), 1894-1897 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Lynch, Peter C. - Inspector of streets salary (2 of 2), 1894-1897 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Mackay, Donald (Executor for Elizabeth R.B. King) against Mary B. Duryea, et al - Estate dispute, 1894 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Magee, William and Peter Delap - North 2nd St. widening assessment, 1894-1895 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Magee, William E., Charles A., and David R. - Sewer property damage (1 of 2), 1894-1897 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Farm bound by New Jersey Ave., Sheffield Ave., Stanley St. (now Wortman Ave.?), and Fairfield St. (now Cozine Ave)
  - Magee, William E., Charles A., and David R. - Sewer property damage (2 of 2), 1894- 1897 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Magill, George H. and other taxpayers and electors - Gravesend annexation (1 of 2), 1894 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Folder (2 of 2) is located in oversized box 239
  - Magill, George H. and other taxpayers and electors - Gravesend annexation (2 of 2), 1894 (Box 239, Folder -)
    Map of the Town of Gravesend
  - Mansfield, Franklin L. - Seaford, Long Island property damage, 1894-1901 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Related to water supply
  - Martins, Lodorico and Caspar Lauro - Water rate dispute, 1894 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Mattarese, Benedetta - Water rate dispute, 1894 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - McCabe, John J. and Edward A. - 249 North Second St. widening assessments, 1894-1895 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Includes Daphney McCabe against John J. McCabe; North 2nd St. is now part of Metropolitan Ave.
  - McCloskey, James P - Stamp clerk dismissal, 1894 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Or McCluskey?
  - McCormack, Richard - 210 St. Marks Ave. sidewalk injury, 1894- 1895 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - McCue, Charles H. - Department of City Works laborer dismissal, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - McGroarty, James - Registrar of Arrears salary dispute, 1894-1895 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - McGuire, Michael - 3rd Ave. (at 3rd St.) car injury, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company
  - Metzgar, David - 176 Fulton St. fire escape violation, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Miller, George F. - 400th anniversary of the discovery of America celebration bill dispute, 1894-1895 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Claim of City of Brooklyn against Miller
  - Miller, John - 233 Williams Ave. sewer property damage, 1894-1895 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mogk, William - Eldert St. opening contract dispute, 1894-1896 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Montague, Peter - 400th anniversary of the discovery of America celebration bill dispute, 1894-1895 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Claim of City of Brooklyn against Montague
  - Moran, John T. - Stationery contract dispute, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Mullins, John - Hudson Ave., Bolivar St., and Fleet St. property damage, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Nassau Electric Railroad Company - Marcy Ave. track dispute (1 of 4), 1894-1896 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Nassau Electric Railroad Company - Marcy Ave. track dispute (2 of 4), 1894-1896 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Nassau Electric Railroad Company - Marcy Ave. track dispute (3 of 4), 1894-1896 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Nassau Electric Railroad Company - Marcy Ave. track dispute (4 of 4), 1894-1896 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Norton, Maria - 42 Somers St. sidewalk injury, 1894 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - O'Brien, Michael - Clerk salary, 1894 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Onderdonk, Horatio G. - Tax sale dispute, 1894 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - O'Reilly, Lawrence - Assessment dispute, 1894 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Ward 24 - Block 206 - Lot 65 (Dean St., between Buffalo Ave. and Ralph Ave.)
  - O'Rourke, John H. - Seaside Athletic Club permit (1 of 2), 1894-1895 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Dispute related to boxing matches
  - O'Rourke, John H. - Seaside Athletic Club permit (2 of 2), 1894- 1895 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Palmer, Noyes F. - Surveyor contract dispute, 1894-1895 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Pease, Richard - Water rate dispute, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Pettus, Edward H. against John H. Pettus - Property sale dispute, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Ward 8 (all) - Block 309 - Lots 6-19; Block 314 - Lots 5-28 (44th and 45th St. between 7th Ave. and 8th Ave.)
  - Popoff, Matilda A., 1894 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Raymond, Geo. W. - Inspector of Streets, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Registrar of Arrears salary increases, 1894- 1895 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    John McMahon, William Furey, Bernard H. Farrell, James J. Haleran, Jere J. Fahey, Michael Rogers, Felix O'Toole,, James J. O'Connor,. James Kerrigan, Benjamin F. Hardenbergh, Thomas J. Dennely, and Joseph H. Delaney
  - Ringrose, Henry W. - Clerk salary, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Rohling, Paul J. - 691 Park Ave. sidewalk injury, 1894- 1895 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Rost, Clara - 347 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Rowland, John H. as Assignee for the benefit of creditors of Frank S. Henderson, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Rusch, Henry M. - 201 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Corner of Deklab Ave.
  - Salmon, John - Vaccination injury, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Schenck, William - Court St. unattended horse injury, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Scholes, Frederick - Ross St. (at Kent Ave.) assessment dispute, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Ward 19 - Block 32 - Lot 1
  - Scrimshaw, Frederick and Charles A. Walters - Public school admittance and vaccination disputes, 1894-1895 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Seaside and Brooklyn Bridge Elevated Railroad Company, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Regarding construction of railroad through High St./Brooklyn Bridge terminus
  - Seeber, Dorothy A. - 697 Jefferson Ave. sidewalk injury, 1894-1896 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Selleck, Ann M. - Tax sale surplus, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Ward 24 - Block 173 - Lot 29 (Douglass St. (now St. Johns Pl.) between Rochester Ave. and Buffalo Ave.)
  - Seton, John and Frank J. - 13th Regiment Armory building construction, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Shanley, George - Volunteer fireman salary dispute, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Sheeren, James - Veteran dismissal, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Albert H. - Estate dispute, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Andrew J. and Charles against The New York Small Stock Company - Wallabout Market dispute, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Charles - Wallabout Market permit dispute, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    City of Brooklyn against Smith
  - Smith, Evan F. - Assistant sanitary inspector dismissal, 1894- 1896 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Freeborn G. - Tax sale dispute, 1894- 1895 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Ward 24 - Block 42 - Lot 18 (Eastern Parkway, between Nostrand Ave. and New York Ave.)
  - Sonnenstrahl, Betsey - Assessment dispute, 1894- 1895 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Myrtle Ave. and Fleet Pl.
  - South Brooklyn Railroad and Terminal Company, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Regarding construction of railroad from the bay near 38th St. to 10th Ave.; Includes Property Owners' Association of the 26th Ward
  - Spaeth, Richard - Constable's bond, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Stack, Thomas W. - Patrolman salary, 1894-1896 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - State of New York - 116 Prospect St. surplus money dispute, 1894-1897 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Ward 2 - Block 17 - Lot 34; Benjamin Croner, Samuel F. Cowdry (or Cowdrey), Paul Pontau, George B. Meade, Halsey R. Meade, James M. Johnson, Henry W. Bates, Nannette Pontau Johnson Harrison, James D. Johnson, James Harrison, Alexander B. Crane, Louise E. Bates, Emily Colder, Frances A. Denike; Includes correspondence to New York Attorney General Theodore E. Hancock
  - Stratton, William - Inspector of Sewers salary, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Sullivan, Mary J. against the Board of Supervisors of the County of Kings, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Sutherland, John - Tax sale dispute, 1894- 1898 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Ward 10 - Block 265 - Lot 33 (Warren St., between Nevins St. and 3rd Ave.)
  - Taber, Charles S. - Tax dispute, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Ward 26 - Block 604 - Lot 8 (Glen St., between Euclid Ave. and Crescent St.)
  - Ulmer, Moses - 19th St. sidewalk injury, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Underhill, Alexander - 121 Navy St. property damage, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Wallabout Market disputes (1 of 2), 1894-1895 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    John E. Liefels, W.W. Kowenhoven, Julia Delaney, Martin Bullwinkle, John H. McNamara, Charles Smith, Henry J. Krusa, Mary E. Davenport, John Husing, and Lohr and Oehl; Includes Peter J. Delaney death record
  - Wallabout Market disputes (2 of 2), 1894-1895 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Wallace, Samuel R. - Fire Department lineman salary, 1894 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Walsh, Edward and Thomas W. Bollas - Fire Department laborer dismissal, 1894-1896 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Waring, John H. - Bath keeper dismissal, 1894 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Weigand, Charles N. - 354 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1894- 1896 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Weil, Henry - Assessment rebate, 1894 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Ward 24 - Block 160 - Lot 2 (Pacific St., between Schenectady Ave. and Utica Ave.)
  - White, Alfred T. vs. Patrick J. Rooney and others, 1894 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Whitman, Frederick - Clerk salary, 1894 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Zeydel, Hugo - 500 Jefferson Ave. sewer property damage, 1894 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Avenue Railroad Company - Electric power, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Baldwin, Charles F. - Clerk salary, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Bay Ridge Park Improvement Company - Tax sale dispute, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Behan, John - City Works laborer salary, 1895-1897 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Behman, Louis C. - Assessment dispute, 1895-1896 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    Ward 9 - Block 188 - Lots 3 and 16 (Corner of 8th Ave. and St. Johns Pl.)
  - Berner, Maria H. - City Hall injury, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    Also Emsie M. Chapin and Augusta Svaguiness
  - Bohen, Anna - Water bills, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    Ward 8 - Block 31 - Lot 8 (4th Ave. and 37th St.)
  - Bond and Mortgage Guarantee Company - Assessment dispute, 1895-1897 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Bower, Samuel - Physician bills, 1895-1896 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Bowitz, Charles - Constable's bond, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Boyce, George P. - Clerk salary, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Brady, Ellen G. - Jay St. and Prospect St. crosswalk injury, 1895-1896 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    See also Brady, Peter P.
  - Brady, Katharine, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Brady, Peter P. - Loss of services of wife, 1895-1896 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    See also Brady, Ellen G.
  - Brasher, William M. - Assessment dispute, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Brennan, Margaret F. - Brooklyn Bridge railroad injury (1 of 2), 1895-1899 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Brennan, Margaret F. - Brooklyn Bridge railroad injury (2 of 2), 1895-1899 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Brodie, Joseph H. - Tax sale surplus, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Ward 25 - Block 138 - Lot 43 (Chauncey St., between Howard Ave. and Saratoga Ave.)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railway Company - Lexington Ave. and Marcy Ave. sewer construction, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company against Daniel J. and John Creem - Lexington Ave. sewer construction dispute, 1895 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    See also Creem, Daniel J. - Sewer construction dispute, 1895
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company and Kings County Elevated Railway Company - Assessment disputes (1 of 6), 1895- 1896 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company and Kings County Elevated Railway Company - Assessment disputes (2 of 6), 1895-1896 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company and Kings County Elevated Railway Company - Assessment disputes (3 of 6), 1895-1896 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company and Kings County Elevated Railway Company - Assessment disputes (4 of 6), 1895-1896 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company and Kings County Elevated Railway Company - Assessment disputes (5 of 6), 1895-1896 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company and Kings County Elevated Railway Company - Assessment disputes (6 of 6), 1895-1896 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Rate of speed, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences - 185 Brooklyn Ave. unsafe building, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Wharf and Warehouse Company - Ferris St. and King St. obstructions, 1895-1896 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Burckle - 197 and 199 Fort Greene Pl. property damage, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Cantero, Mary - 825 Union St. injury, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Or Contero
  - Clerk salary disputes, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    William H. Hogan, William Dempsey, and Patrick M. Conway
  - Cohen, Augustus E. - McKane Flat fire property damage, 1895- 1896 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Colon, William J. - Tax sale dispute, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Ward 9 - Block 13 - Lot 50 (St. Marks Ave., between Carlton Ave. and Vanderbilt Ave.)
  - Coney Island and Brooklyn Railroad Company, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    Regarding Main St. (between Fulton St. and Water St.) repairs
  - Consent and Order Discontinuing Action (various), 1895 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Barbara Adelhardt, Brooklyn Advertising Sign Company, Margaretha Fuller, Stafford D. Gray, Thomas C. Harden, James H. Holmes, Henry Newman, George P. Obach, William O'Keefe
  - Corbin, Austin and others - New Utrecht annexation disputes, 1895 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    65th St., from 5th Ave. to New Utrecht Ave.
  - Corrao, Mary - 337 46th St. property damage, 1895 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Costello, Mary, administratrix of Thomas Carney, 1895-1899 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Gunshot death during the 1895 Trolley Strike
  - County of Kings against Henry H. Adams (County Treasurer) (1 of 6), 1895-1900 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - County of Kings against Henry H. Adams (County Treasurer) (2 of 6), 1895-1900 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - County of Kings against Henry H. Adams (County Treasurer) (3 of 6), 1895-1900 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - County of Kings against Henry H. Adams (County Treasurer) (4 of 6), 1895-1900 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - County of Kings against Henry H. Adams (County Treasurer) (5 of 6), 1895-1900 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - County of Kings against Henry H. Adams (County Treasurer) (6 of 6), 1895-1900 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Cramer, Edward S. - Clerk salary, 1895 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Cranford, John P. - James J. Moran and Company contract dispute, 1895-1896 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Cranford and Company
  - Creem, Daniel J. - Sewer construction dispute, 1895 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Includes contract and specifications for the construction of section 2 of the main sewer extension; See also Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company against Daniel J. and John Creem - Lexington Ave. sewer construction dispute, 1895
  - Cromwell, Frederic - 619 South 7th St. assessment dispute, 1895 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Ward 13 - Block 35 - Lot 22; South 7th St. is now part of Broadway
  - Crummey, Robert - Warrant clerk dismissal (1 of 4), 1895-1897 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Crummey, Robert - Warrant clerk dismissal (2 of 4), 1895-1897 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Crummey, Robert - Warrant clerk dismissal (3 of 4), 1895-1897 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Crummey, Robert - Warrant clerk dismissal (4 of 4), 1895-1897 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Cullen, William - 7th Ave. (between 39th St. and 40th St.) property damage, 1895-1897 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    1868 property records
  - Daleharty, Rhoady and James Devine - 12th Ward Park squatters, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Now Coffey Park in Red Hook
  - Dempsey, William - Barbey St. opening property damage, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Despositto, Antonio, Jr. - Columbia St. sidewalk injury, 1895-1897 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Dewitt, Henry against Atlantic Avenue Railroad Company and City of Brooklyn - New Utrect Ave. injury, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Or DeWitte
  - Diamond, Michael - 332 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Dornbach and Barudio against the estate of A. Wright, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Drake, J. Sterling and Edmund M. Post against the Village of Port Richmond - Assessment Dispute, 1895-1898 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Dunlevy, Ann, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dunne, James - Water rates, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - East River and Atlantic Ocean Railroad Company, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Regarding construction of railroad to Green-Wood Cemetery
  - Ebinger, Frank P.F. - 1833 Fulton St. sewer property damage, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Eiseman, John - Truant Home janitor salary, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Elcock, George S. - Contempt, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Embach, Charles and Sabina - 319 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Englehardt, Valentine - Unpaid mortgage dispute, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Equity Gas Light Company, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Injunction against laying gas pipes
  - Erhard, Charles T. - Investigation of the accounts of the commissioners of the Town of Flatlands (1 of 2), 1895-1896 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Folder (2 of 2) is located in an oversized box.
  - Erhard, Charles T. - Investigation of the accounts of the commissioners of the Town of Flatlands (2 of 2), 1895-1896 (Box 237, Folder -)
    Diagrams of School No. 85 (Evergreen Ave. and Covert St.) and School No. 86 (Harman St. and Irving Ave.)
  - Fire Department laborers' disputes, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Fire Department officers' salaries, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Flatlands police force dismissals, 1895-1896 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Forman, Edward T. - Clerk salary, 1895 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Foster, Henry A. - Clerk salary, 1895 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Franz, Charles - Wooden building within fire limits, 1895 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Frazee, Mary M. - 189 Halsey St. sewer property damage, 1895 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Fredericks, Mary - 121 Kent Ave. sidewalk injury, 1895-1896 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Freel, Edward - Milburn Reservoir construction (1 of 5), 1895 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Edward Freel, Van Brunt Bergen, L. Russell Clapp, Robert Van Buren; See also Freel, Catherine and others - Milburn Reservoir construction, 1900
  - Freel, Edward - Milburn Reservoir construction (2 of 5), 1895 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Freel, Edward - Milburn Reservoir construction (3 of 5), 1895 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Freel, Edward - Milburn Reservoir construction (4 of 5), 1895 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Freel, Edward - Milburn Reservoir construction (5 of 5), 1895 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Fred Hower Brewing Company - Assessment dispute, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Ward 21 - Block 46 - Lots 105-107 (239-268 Pulaski St.)
  - Galvin, Maurice - Tax sale surplus, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Ward 9 - Block 19 - Lot 68 (Pacific St., between Vanderbilt Ave. and Carlton Ave.)
  - Grout, Edward M. - Brooklyn mayoral election dispute (1 of 3), 1895 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Includes William P. Wuest
  - Grout, Edward M. - Brooklyn mayoral election dispute (2 of 3), 1895 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Grout, Edward M. - Brooklyn mayoral election dispute (3 of 3), 1895 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Hale, William H. - Assembly districting dispute, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Hart, Charles - Belgian blocks theft, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    City of Brooklyn against Hart
  - Hart, Charles - Lime storage claim, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Hayden, Henry I., John Schliemann and John W. Cahill - Commissioners of Police and Excise license fees audit (1 of 2), 1895- 1897 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Complaint of City of Brooklyn against Commissioners; See also Audit of accounts, 1905-1906 (Series 6: Miscellaneous)
  - Hayden, Henry I., John Schliemann and John W. Cahill - Commissioners of Police and Excise license fees audit (2 of 2), 1895- 1897 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Hayes, Patrick - Douglass St. assessment petition, 1895 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Ward 24 - Block 45 - Lot 47 (Douglass St., between Rogers Ave. and Nostrand Ave.); This section of Douglass St. is now known as St. Johns Pl.
  - Hellman, Myer (Sisters of Mercy) - New Utrecht annexation dispute, 1895 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    65th St., from 5th Ave. to New Utrecht Ave
  - Hickey, Cornelius J. - Madison St. and Lewis Ave. sewer property damage, 1895-1896 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Hiller, George - 361 Kent Ave. unsafe building, 1895 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Hoffmeier, Joseph against William D. and George H. Andrews - City contract dispute (1 of 2), 1895-1897 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Hoffmeier, Joseph against William D. and George H. Andrews - City contract dispute (2 of 2), 1895-1897 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Hopkins, David - Ashford St. (near New Lots Ave.) greenhouse property damage, 1895 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Imperiale, Rosario - 499 President St. tenant eviction, 1895 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Ward 10 - Block 272 - Lot 24
  - Jamaica and Brooklyn Road Company - Assessment dispute, 1895 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Jaquillard, George and others - Inspection of the Speed of Trolleys compensation, 1895-1896 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Jurgens, Charles A. - Quincy St. assessment petition, 1895 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Ward 7 - Block 54 - Lot 60 (Quincy St., between Nostrand Ave. and Marcy Ave.)
  - Kalbfleisch, M.K. (Estate of) - Tax sale surplus, 1895 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, John - McKane Flat fire property damage, 1895-1896 (Box 50, Folder 8)